[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 23, "question": "An old man sitting on his ass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "I thought I was screaming --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Or is it fraught with pitfalls and potholes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, I'm 50.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Did you find as you get more famous and successful, being very honest and candid is problematic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "RB", "JJS", "CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "You know, it really is, because when I do standup, you're your own boss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Do you find a constant conflict between those two roles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "You know, it's interesting because as a child growing up, and a lot of our great sitcoms come from adaptations of British shows.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Do you mind all of the attention that comes with such a swap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "You know, I -- I like the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Was that me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I'm afraid it was, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "You know, there were things that he said that I was not appropriate to people of my own color.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Which I found disingenuous from somebody else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "What did he mean by that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I think when you understand the material, you understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "I mean, is he much more competitive than people realize, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "I don't -- you know, I don't know if competition is the right word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Do you think he sees you as a threat potentially?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1991"], "PERSON": ["Johnny Carson", "David Letterman"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Isn't that the Holy Grail still?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, if you ask me personally -- I know you didn't ask me -- who I thought should have been the host of the \"Tonight Show\", I think when Johnny Carson left, which I was fortunate enough to do that show with him in 1991, I thought the heir apparent would have been David Letterman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And you still believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay", "Conan O'Brien"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "How did you feel when Conan and Jay had their huge split?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, you know, personally, in my opinion, I don't think that \"The Tonight Show\" should have been offered to Jay -- to Conan O'Brien.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan", "Jay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Do you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "You're going to breastfeed him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "We're going to go outside the family and get somebody to help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Do you miss doing the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "You know what, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "And they both left before you were like 10 or 11 years old?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "But neither your parents nor your grandmother ever told you they loved you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Do you like to be loved by lots of people now, in the way that you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "That's an interesting question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["99 cents"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Do you feel damaged by your upbringing still?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "You know, if I was a can at the store, if I was a can of soup at the store, I would have a dent in me and I would be in that basket that they have at the end of the hall, at the end of the aisle that says these are 99 cents, everything in the can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Did you remember that and how it made you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Yes, I remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "At least she was there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "At least she was there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "So she may not have been perfect by a long way and clearly wasn't able of expressing the kind of love and care that you might have wanted, but she didn't abandon you, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "She did not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Where do you keep her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I keep her in my dressing room.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Do you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "And when you look at her, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I think that I wasted a -- I think that I wasted a lot of time not seeing her when I should've spent more time with her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJR", "CC", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Is there anything you wished you'd said to her that you never got the chance to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I wish that I would've told her that there was nobody that loved her more or anybody that would've protected her more than me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Despite the fact that she wouldn't show that -- do you think she knew?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes, I think she did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Father's Day this year"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Do you ever think about your parents, or are they just something that you blanked out, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "You know, I -- on Father's Day this year, my friend -- a friend of mine, we'd just come back into town.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann", "Ann"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What did marriage bring you, given all that you'd been through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "You know, Ann -- Ann was great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "How much do you think was unfair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "The kidney thing created an awareness of kidney disease, but also of a wife giving a gift to her husband, which I've run into a lot of people that have done that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "It's a problem for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Or is it fraught with pitfalls and potholes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Well, I'm 50, so I think I'm fraught with pitfalls and pot holes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 512, "question": "So, what are you going to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What's going to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I'm going to take Tylenol PMs and sleep a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "How's your daughter been through the whole divorce?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "It's been a little difficult for her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "She was 15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "She was 14, and she's 15 now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Do you think you're a good father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I don't think I -- you know, I always wanted a father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think you have it in you to be the father you'd like to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "For her, yes, because it's my only unconditional love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Lobama"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Would you like to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "We have Obama, we'll have Lobama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Why would you seek public office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "This is a great city, and it's my city.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What do you care about most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "-- bonding the city back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Would that be fair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Well, I'm disappointed with his performance as far as immigration goes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I will go further north.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "You would literally leave the country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I would leave the United States of America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", ":", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Why would you be so drastic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "OPEZ: You know, I like my politicians to actually have a political background, to be politically -- to know politics, to actually have inherited something from working in the political world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 621, "question": "How does she resonate with people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Well, she's --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carlos Santana"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", ":", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Do you find it quite scary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "I think it's scary to me now politically that -- and addressing the immigration thing, again, with Carlos Santana is that we feel like whether we're here -- there are more people in the United States here legally than illegally, but there is a service provided that no one else wants to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "And what is the simple best way of getting somewhere to resolving this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "You know, you have to make us feel like we're important in the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Have you got bigger political aspirations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "I would win -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "I kissed a Smurf and I liked it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "It's an embarrassment of riches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Right, Smurfs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Yes, you said it, absolutely, of course!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "But you didn't actually get to see any of them, right, in the filming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "I did not see any of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Do you like being famous or is it quite restricting now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "I like the fact that I did something that I never imagined that I would do and something I told my friends I was going to do, whether I believed it or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "I'm going to come over a final break and ask you if you could relive one moment in your life, again, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 10 years"], "PERSON": ["Sandra Bullock"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "She sort of found you, didn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "I would say that without Sandra Bullock, I would not have had an opportunity to -- in the last 10 years, to have the career that I've had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "And do you still stay close to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "On occasion we talk, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "She just didn't deserve that, did she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "No, she's a good woman and she had -- has always been very loving to everybody, very fair to everybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Freddie Prinze"]}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "``", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 753, "question": "If you could relive one moment again, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "You know, I -- it's interesting, because it's -- I was a -- I was a huge Freddie Prinze fan, of \"Chico and the Man.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "What have you really learned about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "You know, the one thing that I believe that nothing was ever going to be given to me, and nothing was ever going to be easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]